{
    "subject": "resource/Andriy_Hlushchenko",
    "predicate": "property/name",
    "object": "Andriy Hlushchenko",
    "human_readable": "Andriy Hlushchenko's name is Andriy Hlushchenko.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.98382967710495,
            "question": "What is Andriy Hlushchenko's name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9500654935836792,
            "question": "What is known about Andriy Hlushchenko's background?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.943406343460083,
            "question": "Does Andriy Hlushchenko have any other names?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.933682382106781,
            "question": "Is Andriy Hlushchenko a real person?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9278769493103027,
            "question": "Is there more information available about Andriy Hlushchenko?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8724283576011658,
            "question": "What can you tell me about Andriy Hlushchenko?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8168113231658936,
            "question": "Can you provide any details about Andriy Hlushchenko's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8105147480964661,
            "question": "Are there any public records associated with Andriy Hlushchenko?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7977028489112854,
            "question": "Is Andriy Hlushchenko involved in any specific fields or industries?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.73361736536026,
            "question": "Can you find any online profiles belonging to Andriy Hlushchenko?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Andriy Hlushchenko's name is Andriy Hlushchenko.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1580_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Andriy Hlushchenko involved in any specific fields or industries?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1580_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any public records associated with Andriy Hlushchenko?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1580_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you provide any details about Andriy Hlushchenko's life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1580_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1580_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1580_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1580_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1580_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1580_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1580_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1580_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1580_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1580_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1580_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe query asks if the name \"Andriy Hlushchenko\" is correct, and the documents support this by mentioning \"A notable person with this name is Andriy Oleksandrovych Hlushchenko.\" Therefore, the answer is \"yes\"."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}